[
    {
        "question": "How long do Putal Creek salmon live in the ocean?",
        "options": [
            "2-4 days",
            "2-4 months",
            "2-4 years"
        ],
        "answer": "2-4 years"
    }, {
        "question": "What is true about the muskrat in Putah Creek?",
        "options": [
            "They are frequently seen",
            "Their tails are like paddles",
            "They are a type of duck"
        ],
        "answer": "Their tails are like paddles"
    }, {
        "question": "What do bats in Davis eat for a living?",
        "options": [
            "fruits",
            "small worms",
            "large nocturnal insects"
        ],
        "answer": "large nocturnal insects"
    }, {
        "question": "When can you begin to spot Short-eared Owls?",
        "options": [
            "early morning",
            "late afternoon",
            "late night"
        ],
        "answer": "late afternoon"
    }, {
        "question": "What is the difference between male ducks and female ducks?",
        "options": [
            "Males have curly tail feathers during the winter and spring",
            "Females have bigger beaks and wings",
            "Males have a more vibrant colored feathres than females"
        ],
        "answer": "Males have curly tail feathers during the winter and spring"
    }, {
        "question": "What year was the Davis Centennial Seal installed?",
        "options": [
            "2021",
            "2022",
            "2023"
        ],
        "answer": "2021"
    }, {
        "question": "What map does the Davis Centennial Seal represent in the middle?",
        "options": [
            "Highway 10 and Highway 101",
            "Highway 57 and Highway 210",
            "Highway 80 and Highway 113"
        ],
        "answer": "Highway 80 and Highway 113"
    }, {
        "question": "What does 'Patwin' mean in Wintun language?",
        "options": [
            "Power",
            "Land",
            "People"
        ],
        "answer": "People"
    }, {
        "question": "What does the Davis Centennial Seal NOT symbolize?",
        "options": [
            "Stewardship",
            "Friendship",
            "Community"
        ],
        "answer": "Friendship"
    }, {
        "question": "What did the Patwin people do on purpose to stimulate growth in nature?",
        "options": [
            "cause intentional fire",
            "shower while singing",
            "created artifical wind"
        ],
        "answer": "cause intentional fire"
    }, {
        "question": "What place is preserved for birds to provide their habitat?",
        "options": [
            "Arctic Flyway",
            "Pacific Flyway",
            "Pacific Wetland"
        ],
        "answer": "Pacific Flyway"
    }, {
        "question": "What is causing harm to the birds at the Pacific Flyway?",
        "options": [
            "climate change",
            "habitat loss",
            "both climate change and habitat loss"
        ],
        "answer": "both climate change and habitat loss"
    }
    
    

]
